rootsin.com 2016-11-01

# Privacy Policy - Rootvinn

Privacy Policy of Rootvinn.com would provide you with a clear picture that how do we use the information provided by you at the time of filling up registration form and accepting terms and conditions laid by Rootvinn.com.   
Since we are faithful to the privacy policies and statements put down by Rootvinn.com, we even respect your concern towards the information.

In order to offer you with a unique surfing experience on Rootvinn.com, we may require collecting some personal information from you. Additionally, we may require some information even to generate your account and identify yours. 

**Reasons for collecting personal data**

The main purpose of Rootvinn.com collecting personal information is just to provide you with the personalized services. Type of information which we collect is as follows:

We use a range of online technologies and other software to understand about your usage, which even helps us in providing an indirect feedback about our portal from your end. 

If any registered user or a guest viewer visits Rootvinn.com, his/her date, time and IP address is recorded at backend. This helps us to take immediate action at the time of any spam taking place.

When you register for our services we require your personal details to create a unique account ID for you.

**Using your information**

Any user providing personal information to Rootvinn.com need to know that information provided by you are used for following purpose.

We may even use this information to take your personalized feedback which will help us to modify our services. Further, we might even provide industry wise segregation for our clients in the services which again depend on such personal feedbacks. 

**Managing your own information**

We will definitely provide you with the choices when we ask for any personal information from you wherever possible.

You are always allowed to change or modify your details just by logging into your account though Rootvinn.com would have a complete record of your modification or deletion of the information.

We hold back your information till you don’t completely delete your account or give complete information about you.

We take complete care and try to resist our site from any spam, hackers or any unauthorized usage or access. In case if you wish to write us anything regarding these privacy statements, feel free to mail us on info@rootsin.com or you can even follow our contact us link to mail us on general mailbox or call us at any point of time. 

For any further queries kindly visit the site www.rootvinn.com.
